If they lived in the same century, they'd be perfect for each other.
Kate & Leopold is a romance, comedy, fantasy film directed by James Mangold.
When her scientist ex-boyfriend discovers a portal to travel through time -- and brings back a 19th-century nobleman named
Leopold to prove it -- a skeptical Kate reluctantly takes responsibility for showing Leopold the 21st century.
The more time Kate spends with Leopold, the harder she falls for him.
But if he doesn't return to his own time, his
absence will forever alter history.
Kate McKay, played by Meg Ryan.
Leopold, played by Hugh Jackman.
Stuart Besser, played by Liev Schreiber.
Charlie McKay, played by Breckin Meyer.
Darci, played by Natasha Lyonne.
J.J. Camden, played by Bradley Whitford.
Kate & Leopold is a 2001 American romantic comedy science fiction film that tells a story of a physicist by the name of Stuart (Liev Schreiber), who accidentally pulls his great‑great‑grandfather,
Leopold (Hugh Jackman), through a time portal from 19th‑century New York to the present, where Leopold and Stuart's ex‑girlfriend, Kate (Meg Ryan), fall in love with each other.
The film explores themes of new york city, time travel,
duke, fish out of water, falling in love.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.